

### Maksim Svistukhin

#### **DETAILS**

n Prague, Czech Republic

+420 608594057

#### **SKILLS**

**Excelent communication** 

Front-end development

Web design

Direct sales

Solution design

Team management

### **LANGUAGES**

English

C1

Czech

C1

Russian

NATIVE

### **TECH SKILLS**

HTML CSS JavaScript

React Git

SCSS Sketch Adobe CS

Webflow Figma

#### PROFILE :

First of all, I am a strong professional in communication at all levels. I have extensive experience in team management and sales, as well as excellent visualisation abilities and decent skills in SW development. Overall, I can describe myself as a person, passionate about finding solutions for rather wide range of possible issues.

### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

### Freelance Web Designer

2/2019 - Current

Prague, Czech Republic

- · Creating web applications design using the latest UI/UX trends in Figma
- · Development using a combination of HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- · Managing and maintaining client websites

## Logistics/Sales manager

12/2017 - 2/2019

Prague Group Adventures s.r.o.

Prague, Czech Republic

- · Maintaining communication with service providers, tour guides and clients.
- · Recruitment and training of staff
- Managing a team of 30 employees
- · Maintaining and establishing plans for selling ancillary services to the end customer

# **Team-leader (Customer support )** 6/2016 – 10/2017

XEROX o.s.

Prague, Czech Republic

- · Assist management with hiring procedures and training of new team members.
- · Assist with team member problems and monitor work for quality and compliance
- Communicate deadlines and goals to team members

# **Customer Support Advisor**

11/2014 - 6/2016

XEROX o.s.

Prague, Czech Republic

- Advising customers on technical matters
- Advertising the product
- · Maintain positive relationships with customers to ensure customer loyalty

### Travel agent/Coordinator

2/2014 - 12/2019

Wild East Travels

Prague, Czech Republic

- Meeting of the incoming groups
- Training of the newcomers
- · Maintaining appropriate relationships with service providers
- · Conducting sales of ancillary services

# Luxury Retail Sales Manager

5/2011 - 8/2012

Boutique Vittoria Samara, Russia

- Support sales professionals in closing sales
- · Partner with sales professionals to meet their individual sales plans and KPI
- Remain current and knowledgeable of industry trends, to determine strategic opportunities to maximize sales within the market

## **EDUCATION**

### Operations management, bc

Samara State Technical University Samara, Russia

### Management, bc

Czech University of Life Sciences Prague